The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Planet Tian Yun\NAlliance Star System
Planet Tian Yun's spiritual energy is so dense
that it's overflowing.
Planet Suzaku is not even comparable to it.
Many powerful cultivators must live on it.
To avoid being found out as an Ancient God,
my original body will stay hidden.
There seems to be
some kind of destructive energy in this mist.
If I recklessly charge in,
it will attack me relentlessly.
I'm looking for Senior All-Seer.
Fellow cultivator, come in.
Master has been expecting you.
I never told anyone where I was going.
Could it be that Senior All-Seer
possesses divination abilities
and calculated my arrival today ?
Heavenly Fate Sect
Wang Lin of planet Suzaku
requests an audience with Senior All-Seer.
Zhao Xingsha\NMiddle stage Soul Transformation\NHeavenly Fate Sect Purple Division disciple
Master,
this person is just an honorary disciple,
why do you want him to take the trials ?
Back then, I took him as disciple on a whim
so it created a seed of karma for our relation.
I didn't expect that in just 100 years,
he would've already reached this stage.
He isn't simple...
He has good fortune
to have caught Master's eye.
If he passes the 3 trials,
take him to the Purple Cloud Pavilion.
Zhou Wan\NMiddle stage Soul Transformation\NHeavenly Fate Sect Purple Division disciple
Is a native from a wasted planet
worthy of Master's teachings ?
Master values talent.
If this Wang Lin is extraordinary,
taking him as a disciple
is only natural.
Junior Brother Sun Yun,
it seems Master has really lost all faith in you…
Wang Lin,
if you want to see Master,
you'll have to undergo the 3 trials.
Do you dare to try ?
Why wouldn't I ?
The Human Trial
tests the Dao Heart.
Human Trial
How is
the Dao Heart tested ?
Wan'er...
So it uses the heart's desires
to manifest illusions.
But how does one pass the Human Trial ?
This trial isn't difficult.
Whether you calm your heart
or slash through the illusion,
the trial will be cleared.
But Senior Brother,
do you know what Sun Yun did back then ?
He chose to seek the Dao.
Sun Yun became Master's direct disciple of the Purple Division.
He really was a genius.
How many geniuses like Sun Yun are there in this world ?
Tie Zhu !
Father,
Mother.
We are going to the mountains.
Is it just the two of you ?
Will you be safe ?
It's fine,
many people from the village are going together.
Right.
If we're lucky,
we might even get a roe deer pelt
to make a jacket.
Tie Zhu,
what are you carving ?
Yes...
What am I carving ?
Why can't I remember ?
I only remember
that it was something very important.
I don't want to let go of this obsession.
Something's happened !
A tiger has killed people !
Dead...
They're all dead...
They were fine when they left...
Father...
How did this happen ?
Mother...
So that's what
the Human Trial is...
Tie Zhu !
Each time my wood carving breaks,
the cycle starts again.
And the cycles are endless...
Every time,
they leave me in the same way.
Since you have seen through it,
why didn't you break the illusion to come out ?
You can't build without breaking.
Break it and recreate it.
Major destruction leads to major creation.
Dawn is a metaphor of rebirth.
Rebirth...
What's old ?
What's new ?
The 84th cycle is about to begin.
Are you sure you want to continue ?
Of course.
This child
is really good...
The Human Trial that I made
may be called a trial
but is in reality an opportunity.
If one seeks the Dao during the trial,
the Dao Heart will become indestructible.
Sun Yun only sought of the Dao for 67 days back then.
Senior Brother,
this child is bad news.
Maybe...
No matter who you are,
get out !
The true meaning of the Human Trial
is to seek the Dao with your heart.
Being yourself
and not fearing your true heart.
Not rejecting your heart
is the true meaning of freedom.
Earth Trial
I'm the guardian of the Earth Trial.
Defeat me,
and you may continue.
It seems that the number of guardians I can defeat
is used to gauge the strength of my cultivation.
Someone's been spying on me.
These Earth Trial and Heaven Trial
might be dangerous.
I give up
the Earth Trial.
Quite clever.
If you dared to continue,
I would've used this opportunity to kill you.
At least now,
you've lost your qualification to become a disciple.
Stop it.
Master's order.
What !?
Heaven Trial
The Heaven Trial
tests the domain.
I got so far
by making a domain with a small part of a heavenly Dao
that I was able to understand.
Can the All-Seer manifest the root of that heavenly Dao ?
What kind of power does he possess ?
But I don't want this experience
to sabotage my domain.
I give up
the Heaven Trial.
Junior Brother Wang Lin,
I am Zhao Xingsha.
Since I entered the sect earlier,
you may call me Senior Brother.
Greetings, Senior Brother.
Junior Brother, follow me.
Master has instructed me
to guide you to the Purple Cloud Pavilion.
Senior Brother,
how many disciples
does Senior All-Seer have ?
The Master's disciples
are all categorized by 7 colors.
Just our Purple Division
has over a million disciples.
This is
the Purple Division of the Heavenly Fate Sect.
Among the 7 divisions,
our Purple Division is the weakest.
You will understand why
very quickly.
Junior Brother Wang Lin,
go west from here
to the Purple Cloud Pavilion.
You will find it easily.
I still have important things to do
so I won’t accompany you.
Purple Cloud Pavilion
Jin Ye\NHeavenly Fate Sect Purple Division disciple\NEarly stage Soul Transformation
Who are you ?
Leave !
I am Wang Lin, a new disciple of the Purple Division.
Master instructed me to live in the Purple Cloud Pavilion.
Scram ! Don't take a single step
within 100 li from the Purple Cloud Pavilion !
She dares to deny
the All-Seer's order ?
Senior Brother, you have been away for too long.
They're trying to take your Purple Cloud Pavilion now...
But as long as I am here,
I will not let it happen !
Someone tried to sabotage me within the 3 trials.
I didn't pass them
but was still allowed into the sect.
Now, the Purple Cloud Pavilion is guarded.
With the All-Seer's power,
he must know all of this.
Since he chooses to stand by and watch,
that means he is still testing me.
3 days later
Elders,
it's here.
Who dared to make a cave
without an Elder's permission ?
Come out now !
We are the Purple Division's Disciplinary Elders.
You have one incense stick of time
to destroy this cave !
If you don't,
you will be punished.
Although the cave is destroyed,
you still violated the sect's rules.
Come with us now,
we will decide your punishment !
You've picked the wrong person to mess with.
I just wanted to cultivate in peace.
But I cannot endure your provocations.
Wang Lin !
How dare you attack a Disciplinary Elder ?
Seven Broken Stars !
Grandson, stand still for your grandpa !
If you dare to move,
I'll slice your head off !
A madman...
He's a madman !
Who used to live in the Purple Cloud Pavilion ?
1000 years ago,
a peerless genius appeared in the Purple Division.
His name was Sun Yun,
he lived in the Purple Cloud Pavilion.
100 years ago, after he betrayed the sect,
the Purple Cloud Pavilion became vacant.
What does this Sun Yun have to do with me ?
Nothing.
But Master has always taken a single direct disciple
from each one of the 7 divisions.
They're the only ones that will receive his true teachings
and are called the Seven Sons of Tian Yun.
Master once said that
the next person that lives in the Purple Cloud Pavilion
will become a Son of Tian Yun.
So that's why everyone's been so hostile towards me.
I...I've told you everything,
please spare my life !
Since waiting here is useless,
I will turn this place upside down
to let everyone know
that I am not someone to mess with.
From now on,
this pavilion
Purple Forest Pavilion\NHeavenly Fate Sect\NPurple Division
Purple Forest Pavilion
shall be renamed Purple Forest Pavilion.
Note: The "Lin" in "Wang Lin" is the character for "forest".
Wang Lin...
I'm going to...
kill you !!!
You're just a fool that's being manipulated.
Stop it !
As expected, they've come.
3 Middle stage Soul Transformation
and 1 Late stage.
Zhao Xinmeng\NHeavenly Fate Sect Purple Division disciple\NLate stage Soul Transformation
Junior Brother Wang Lin,
you just entered the sect.
How could you have already killed Fifth Sister ?
How could you have harmed a fellow disciple ?
Senior Brother,
no need to waste words with him.
I will clean up the sect for Master !
So you're the one that interfered
in my trials.
You're a native from a wasted planet !
Before you die, let me show you
what a real spell looks like !
Forbidden spell...
Immortal Demonic Body !
Die !
Demonic Finger !
How could he
possess such a spell ?!
What an overbearing finger spell.
He's just an arrogant Junior that shows no respect for Elders !
God Slaying Chariot !
I just entered the sect
but I've encountered so many obstacles.
This is not a coincidence.
The only one who could orchestrate disciples and Elders
so seamlessly
Senior Brother, that's you.
Is Senior Brother worried that I'll become one of the Seven Sons of Tian Yun ?
Is that why you're doing all this ?
Don't spout nonsense !
What the hell is this thing !?
What a formidable Heavenly Beast !
Greetings, Master.
When I saw you on planet Suzaku back then,
I said I'd take you as an honorary disciple for 100 years.
But now, I have changed my mind.
Are you willing to become my disciple
to cultivate the great Dao of the heavens ?
Will you become the direct disciple of the Purple Division ?
Disciple Wang Lin
pays respects to Master.
Good.
You must have had a demonic cultivator beside you
which has tainted you with his demonic aura.
Disciple knows someone like that
but we've parted ways.
It doesn't matter.
In my eyes,
there's no distinction between righteous, evil, immortal and demon.
One only needs
to follow their natural desires.
Heavenly fate, heavenly fate !
Everything in the world depends on fate.
As long as you have a Dao Heart,
you can cultivate any of the infinite Daos that exist.
Disciple will remember your teachings.
I will celebrate my birthday in 3 months.
I will take the opportunity to announce I accepted you as my disciple.
Get ready.
The cultivators of planet Tian Yun have profound cultivation and spells...
The relations in the sect are complex...
It's far more dangerous than Suzaku.
Even though the All-Seer has accepted me as his disciple,
I must not let my guard down
against the Purple Division.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?